CURRICULUM VITAE			
NAME Antonio Trabalza	ACTUAL POSITION Freelance Full Stack Developer & Consultant		
https://antoniotrkdz.github.io antoniotrabalza@gmail.com TEL +44(0)7577833827 +393204516210			
EDUCATION/QUALIFICATIONS			
INSTITUTION AND LOCATION	DEGREE	YEAR(S)	FIELD OF STUDY
Founders & Coders London	London Curriculum	2017	Full stack web development
Imperial College London	Course	2015	C for Science
NIMR London - MRC	Course	2014	Successful Grant Writing
Imperial College London	License	2010	ASpA Personal License
"Sapienza" University of Rome	PhD	2006-2009	Neuroscience
"Sapienza" University of Rome	B.A.	1999-2005	General and Experimental Psychology

About

I am a web developer with Neuroscience research experience. I am passionate about Science and Technology and I love the free software world: GNU/Linux OS (Devuan & Void) – (Neo)Vim. I am passionate Blockchain and Artificial Intelligence.

I write JavaScript, mainly Node.js (back-end). I use VUE.js on front-end. I also know Java EE and some experience with Ruby (on Rails). I also love to use Containers and Virtual Machines, and with circuits and components I have fun making IoT and embedded projects (Arduino and Raspberry Pi).

Skills:

Programming - Github profile name: antoniotrkdz

- Javascript ES6, HTML5 e CSS3.
- Node.js Hapi.js, Express.js.
- VUE.js, React, Redux, JQuery and Handelbars.
- Java EE and Spring.
- Node-RED, embedded and IoT.
- Ruby on Rails.
- Wordpress.
- Shell scripting.
- BEM, Bootstrap 3.* and 4, Material Design.
- PostgreSQL and MySQL.
- Testing: Rspec, QUnit, Tape, Jest, Codecov.
- Building, deployment and CI: Webpack, Heroku, Travis CI.
- C relatively to Arduino prototyping.
- Python relatively to Raspberry Pi prototyping.
- · R Statistics.
- OpenSCAD (3D design and printing).
- Macro language for FIJI/ImageJ2 Tools for image analisys (microscopy) & pattern recognition (see https://antoniotrkdz.github.io).

IT / System Administration

- Gnu/Linux Operating System.
- Installation and Administration of Ubuntu, Debian, Gentoo, Fedora, CentOS and Devuan, both Desktop and Server.
- Configuration and (remote) administration of LAMP and similar stacks, tests and log analysis (SAR tools).
- Network analysis (nmap, netstat, netcat, tcpdump, wireshark).
- Basic AWS skills.

- Virtualization VirtualBox and Qemu/KVM.
- Docker Containers.
- Very good hardware knowledge.
- · Good Electronics knowledge.

Interpersonal, Planning and Problem solving

- Presentation of code, tech and related subjects and product pitch, both written and Spoken.
- Dissemination of research findings in international journals publications, and conferences.
- Managing, planning and reporting of my own work and supervised students (20+) within regular team and departmental meetings.
- Management of internal and external collaborations.
- Design and planning of novel experiments to overcome problems related to PhD and PostDoc research activities.
- Management of Research funds.
- Fluent English both written and spoken.

Current Projects:

Since May 2020:

Part-time Front end and Node-RED Developer – "Termo-controllo" Raspberry Pi and Node-RED based thermo scanner device with face recognition and (remote) entrance management.

Officine Innesto – Torino – https://www.officine.cc

"Termo-controllo" device - See below.

Since June 2020:

Part-time Project manager & Developer on ASTRA: ASTRA is a project funded by the Italian Ministry of development (MiSE) "Fabbrica Intelligente" framework. It is an advanced training system using Blockchain to certificate accomplishments and qualifications.

Companies involved are:

4DLabs: Immersive Simulators, Virtual and Augmented Reality used to train people in hazardous environments – https://www.4dlabs.it

Next2U: Solutions and systems for non-invasive and non-contact monitoring of psychophysiological state – https://www.next2u-solutions.com

Dimensione Solare (employer): Hi-tech hardware and software solutions and products.

https://www.dimensionesolare.it

Past Working Experience:

July 2019 to February 2020:

Full stack developer - Engine S.r.l. - Serre di Rapolano (SI).

I Developed a cloud system to manage traffic cameras remotely: Celeritas Cloud.

To be deployed during 2020/2021.

September 2018 to February 2019:

System admin and developer – Dimensione Solare S.r.l. – Notaresco (TE).

I wrote the ASTRA project. Funded by MiSE.

May to August 2018:

Web developer – Nebulab.it – Pescara.

February 2018 to May 2018:

Web development and Javascript teacher – Turn into Coders – Torino.

February 2017 to December 2017:

Web developer – Founders & Coders C.I.C. – London.

Stem ambassador web development teacher – London.

May 2016 to February 2017:

Postdoc research associate at Department of cellular and molecular neuroscience, Imperial College Faculty of Medicine – London, funded by BTRC – Brain Tumour Research Committee.

June 2014 to November 2015:

Postdoc research associate at MRC – Clinical Sciences Centre, Imperial College Hammersmith Hospital Campus – London, funded by MRC core funding.

May 2010 to March 2014:

Postdoc research associate at Department of cellular and molecular neuroscience, Imperial College Faculty of Medicine – London, funded by ERC grant - "Improved retrograde lentiviral vectors for gene therapy in motor neuron disease".

Teaching Experience:

Two courses (2007/2008 and 2008/2009) relative to lectures of Applied Biology course of the Faculty of Psychology – University "Sapienza" of Rome – 3 lectures (6 hours total) per year. One course (10 hours total) of Web Development for children age 10-16 years. STEM ambassador activity – London (2017).